(Seibert:)and I sympathize,
but the hard facts are,
(Seibert:)occasionally,
we have to shake a few hands
(Seibert:)and kiss a few butts
to raise money for our research.
I don't care;
it's demeaning.
(Sheldon:)And I refuse to be
trotted out and shown off
(Sheldon:)like a prize hog
at the Texas State Fair.
(Sheldon:)Which, by the way, is something
you don't want to attend
(Sheldon:)wearing a Star Trek
ensign's uniform.
(Seibert:)All right,
(Seibert:)let me put it this way.
(Seibert:)You're gonna put on a suit,
you're gonna come to this party,
(Seibert:)and you're gonna
explain your research
(Seibert:)to a bunch of old people,
(Seibert:)or I swear to God,
I'll blind you with a hot spoon,
like they did  to that little boy
in Slumdog Millionaire.
(Raj:)Oh, you don't want that.
(Seibert:)So, Saturday night!
(Seibert:)It's gonna be
off the hook.
Ugh!
(Seibert:)Get over it.
(Raj:)Oh, boy!
(Raj:)Tator tots and
a party invitation?
(Raj:)What a great day!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪